http://www.ronwiser.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Privacy and protection of your personal information is important to us. We will not rent, trade, sell, or otherwise barter the personal information you choose to share with us. When you visit thewiserfinancialgroup.com, you can surf the site and access information about our financial services without revealing your identity. In order to improve the thewiserfinancialgroup.com site, we use IP log files to conduct anonymous web traffic analysis, and "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. For some web pages that require authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.
While we use cookies to track your visit to thewiserfinancialgroup.com, and our hosted web server automatically logs the IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided us with personal information.
Your Consent
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by The Wiser Financial Group. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of how we use your information to better serve you.
My AccountPrivacyLegalDisclaimer
© The Wiser Financial Group6100 Stadium Drive, Kalamazoo MI 49009269.372.1430 | 800.292.1472Site Made in Michigan by NK
Securities offered through Kestra Investment Services, LLC (Kestra IS), member FINRA/SIPC. Investment advisory services offered through Kestra Advisory Services, LLC (Kestra AS), an affiliate of Kestra IS. Neither Kestra IS nor Kestra AS are affiliated with The Wiser Financial Group nor any other entity referenced herein. Neither Kestra IS nor its affiliates provide legal or tax advice and are not Certified Public Accounting firms.
This site is published for residents of the United States only. Registered Representatives of Kestra Investment Services, LLC and Investment Advisor Representatives of Kestra Advisory Services, LLC, may only conduct business with residents of the states and jurisdictions in which they are properly registered. Therefore, a response to a request for information may be delayed. Not all of the products and services referenced on this site are available in every state and through every representative or advisor listed. For additional information, please contact our Compliance department at 737-443-2582.
The above links are provided for your information only. As they are provided by third parties, Kestra Investment Services, LLC does not endorse, nor accept any responsibility for the content. Kestra IS does not independently verify this information, nor do we guarantee its accuracy or completeness.
